dansdata.com 2001-04-11

# Privacy statement

[More **FREE** stuff than you can poke a stick at is at Free2Try.com!](http://free2try.com/?userid=5753)

Want to make 15% per annum? [Be a Fool](http://ads.websponsors.com/?u=5753&o=1592), and get valuable financial [freebies](http://ads.websponsors.com/?u=5753&o=1592) too!

|  | Dan's Data has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for [Dan's Data](http://www.dansdata.com/).

### Information Automatically Logged

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Dan's Data does not use cookies for any other purpose. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.  
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Dan's Data is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

### Contacting Dan's Data

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [dan@dansdata.com](mailto:dan@dansdata.com).

### Flycast statement

__

__Dan's Data works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to<http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>.

.

|  |
